{
  "title": "Digital cameras, photography and picture vocabulary",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "To save ........ power, your camera will enter standby mode if no operations are performed for a preset length of time.",
      "answers": ["battery", "tripod", "memory", "lens"],
      "correct": "battery"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Pictures stored on the ........ can be printed in the same way as photos taken with a film camera.",
      "answers": ["memory", "zoom", "flash", "memory card"],
      "correct": "memory card"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "When the ........ is on, pictures are taken ten seconds after the shutter-release button is pressed.",
      "answers": ["tripod", "view finder", "power switch", "self-timer"],
      "correct": "self-timer"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "One key to cleaning the ........ of your camera is not to touch it with your fingers.",
      "answers": ["zoom", "eyelet", "lens", "tripod"],
      "correct": "lens"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Pictures can be ........ by inserting a memory card containing images into a printer or having prints made at a digital photo lab.",
      "answers": ["taken", "shot", "printed", "exposed"],
      "correct": "printed"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "The ........ on your camera may not be able to light the entire subject at distances of less than 40 centimeters.",
      "answers": ["lens", "flash", "zoom", "microphone"],
      "correct": "flash"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Pictures taken with a digital camera are stored as ........ files.",
      "answers": ["image", "memory", "compression", "analogue"],
      "correct": "image"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "To reduce the amount of memory each image occupies, pictures are ........ as they are saved to the memory card. ",
      "answers": ["enlarged", "compressed", "spread out", "deleted"],
      "correct": "compressed"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Pictures are stored in ........ created automatically by the camera.",
      "answers": ["memory", "displays", "folders", "focus"],
      "correct": "folders"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "If your camera fails to ......... as expected, you should check the troubleshooting section of your instruction manual.",
      "answers": ["photograph", "snapshot", "function", "display"],
      "correct": "function"
    }
  ]
}
